New York State Department of Labor Files 6152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Petition - Ame Stores Inc. et al., with place of business in the State of New York Article 19 of the Labor Law (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Petition - Ame Stores, Inc. et al. Case No. 1448-39 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Petition - Iris Valet Services, Inc. Case No. 1552-39 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Industrial Code Proposed Rule No. 36 Relating to the Hours of Women in Book Binderies and Allied Industries (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Relating to the Hours of Women in Book Binderies and Allied Industries (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Petitions relative to Directory Order No. 7 governing minimum wage standards in the Retail Trade Industry (Box 9, Folder 42)
- The New York Farm Bureau Appeal against MP Catherwood, Industrial Commissioner Respondent (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Appeal of Kiamesha Concord, Inc., etc. to review under sect. 657 of Labor Law Part 138 of Official Compilation of Codes, Rules and Regulations, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Board of Standards and Appeals - Department of Labor Petition of Harry J Hutchins, etc. Factual Brief (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Dalsi, Inc., etc.., et al., petitioners Min Wage Order 9 in article 19 of Labor Law (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Electrolux Corporation Real Silk Hosiery Mills, Inc. The Hoover company Good Humor Corporation (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Petition of James Scolamerio and Myron Goldberg (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Application of Sidney Seligman, Edwin K. Latz and Israel A Latz under Firm name Seligman & Latz, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Petition of Herbert Vander Vate, et al. (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Petition Herbert Vander Vate et al. with place of business I the state of new York (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Wells Plaza Corp, et al. Sect. 110 Min wage Order No. 6-d (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Wells Plaza Corporation doing business as Belmont Plaza Hotel, et al. Application (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Wells Plaza Corporation doing business as Belmont Plaza Harry J Hutchins Marine Laundry Case No. 47-39 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- New York State Camp Directors Association Inc. Case No. MWA 1 67 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Petition Mary Lincoln Candies, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Board of Standards and Appeals - Department of Labor Petition of Mary Lincoln Candies, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 57)
- C M Barret & Son, et al. (Box 9, Folder 58)
- J W Mays Inc. (Box 9, Folder 59)
- NYS Restaurant Association Inc. against Martin P Cather wood (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Petition for a Review of Directory Order No. 5 of the Industrial Commissioner of the SNY on Min Wages in the Restaurant Industry (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Supreme Court Appellate Division Third Judicial Department Decision handed down Jan 9 Re: AWA Pharmacy and others, Arcadie Inc., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Labor Law Table of Contents (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Petition of Fisher-Beer company, et al. Validity and Reasonableness of Directory Order No. 7 Article 19 Min Wage (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Laws Relating to Apprenticeship New York State 14 - 0001, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- History of New York State Apprenticeship Council, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Booklet: Future Craftsmen 14 - 0003, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Apprenticeship in New York State 14 - 0004 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Apprenticeship in New York State 14 - 0005 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Memo to: Trade Unionists from: New York State Department of Labor 14 - 0006 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- What the Grange Masters of New York State Say About the Employment of School Children from Cities Upon Farms 17 - 0001, 1917 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 1b How Up - State New York Boys and Girls Earned Money 17 - 0002, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Partial Lists of Places of Employment Given on Reports to New York Child Labor Committee by Children Under 14 Years of Age Inclusive Who Worked During Summer of 1935, 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- School Children as Harvest Hands in 1941 17 - 0004, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Summary of Impressions Gained Through a Trip of Eighteen Days Visiting Truck Farms in Central New York State July 19th - August 5th, 1939 17 - 0005 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Report of the Secretary to the Board of Directors of New York Child Labor Committee 17 - 0007, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Booklet: Truck Farm Child Worker in New York State 17 - 0007, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- New York Child Labor Committee 105 East 22d Street New York, N.Y. 17 - 0008, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Summary of a Two Weeks Investigation Tenement Home Work - A Vanishing Industry 17 - 0009, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Docs Relating to Child Labor in NY 17 - 0010, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Homework - Sabatini Case 17 - 0011, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Booklet: State Mediation Board Policies and Procedures Labor Arbitrations 18 - 0001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Arbitration Under the Taft - Hartley Act 18 - 1001, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- The Eight - Hour Day in the Light of History 20 - 0001 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Memorandum to Dr. Patton 20 - 0002, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  Scope and Contents
  Enclosed is a copy of the data concerning the brush industry obtained by Mr. Bisom in Albany, on July 25, 1939.
- Accidents to Minors 20 - 0003 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Memorandum for Commissioner Andrews 20 - 0004, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Comparison between 1925 and 1927 Censuses of Manufacturers 20 - 0005, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- A Plan for Shop Safety, Sanitation and Health Organization 20 - 0006, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Industrial Migration 20 - 0007, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Trade Union Schedules Trade Agreements 20 - 0008, 1897-1916 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Analysis of Census of Manufactures for New York State and New York City 20 - 0009, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Labor in the Manufacturing Industries of New York State 20 - 0010, 1919-1933 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Prelininary Draft of Final Report of the New York State Citizens' Committee of One Hundred for Children and Youth 21 - 0001, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Questions Raised by Dispensation Request 21 - 0002, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Dupl of 01 - 0010 in Box 1 Item Moved There 21 - 0003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- The Labor Management Relations Act, 1947 21 - 0004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Analyzing the Contention of the Gloversville Glove Industry that Homework Order No. 4 Is Curtailing Production 21 - 0005, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Guides for the Administration of the Equal Pay Law 21 - 0006, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Library Background to the Promulgation of Order No. 5 Regulation Homework on Direct Mail Operations 21 - 0007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Miss Stouts' Memo File 21 - 0008, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0009, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Information for Mailler Committee Hearing February 13 on Control of Strikes During the Emergency 21 - 0010, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Nonprofit Organizations Covered by the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law, First Quarter, 1972 21 - 0011, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- State of New York Department of Labor Inter-Office Memorandum 21 - 0012, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Development of Child Labor Laws Applying to Work in Factories and on Farms, New York State 21 - 0013, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Work - Injury Experience on Completed Construction Projects Under the Safety Consultant Program of the New York State Department of Labor, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Development of Child Labor Legislation 1/ 21 - 0015, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- State Laws Regulating Child Labor in Agriculture 21 - 0016, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Outline of Proposed Case Studies of the Employment of Older Workers 21 - 0017, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- New York State Department of Labor Docs 21 - 0018, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Minimum-Wage Research 21 - 0019, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Survey of Collective Bargaining Agreements Covering Foremen 21 - 0020 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Research in the Field of Women and Children in Industry 21 - 0021, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Coverage Under the Confectionery Order in Regard to: Christo Poulos and Co., Inc. 21 - 0022, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- The Structure and Organization of the Division of Research and Statistics of the New York State Dept. of Labor and Addendum to Structure and Organization Report 21 - 0023, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Futures Committee Final Report on the Reorganization of the Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0024, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Steering Committee Final Report on the Reorganization of the Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0025, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Memorandum: Community Service Center Final Report 21 - 0026 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Survey of Earnings and Hours in New York State Industry Made by the Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0027, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Division of Research and Statistics Occupation of Puerto Ricans in New York City 21 - 0028, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Health of Women Night Workers A Statement of the Research Problem 21 - 0029, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Inter - Office Memorandum Proposed Minimum Wage Orders 21 - 0030, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Minimum-Wage Research 21 - 0031, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Possible Survey of Wages and Hours in Hospitals and Related Institutions, Under the Minimum Wage Law 21 - 0032, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0033, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- 21 - 0034 Preliminary Tables on the Out - Migration of Industry, New York State, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Background Material on a Statutory Minimum Wage Law 21 - 0035, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Availability of Workmen's Compensation Data on Accident Cause 21 - 0036, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- U.S. Dept of Labor. Women's Bureau Letter from Frieda S 21 - 0037, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- New York (State) Department of Labor. Division of Research and Statistics. 21 - 0038, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Recent Research Activity in Selected Aspects of Manpower Research 21 - 0039, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Labor Market Information Sources for Manpower Planners 21 - 0040, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- (Exhibit A) Some Proposals on the Compilation of Safety Order and Accident Statistics 21 - 0041, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Memorandum to: Members of Advisory Committee on Research 21 - 0042, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Employment and Training Services for Dislocated Workers 21 - 0043, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- JTPA IIB Summer Youth Employment and Training Program 21 - 0044, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Job Training Services for Youth and Adults (JTPA IIA) 21 - 0045, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Local 1473 American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees 21 - 0046, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Research Program 21 - 0047, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Notes on Legislation for Compulsory Cash Disability Insurance 21 - 0048, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Some Research Possibilities and Other Subjects Relating to the Work of the Division of Research and Statistics 21 - 0049, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- An Outline of the Problems of Migratory Farm Labor 21 - 0050, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Average Hours of Work in Selected Defense Related Industries in New York State in Relation to National Manpower Policies on Hours of Work for Maximum Protection 21 - 0051, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Technique for Securing Adjusted Manufacturing Productions Worker Series for New York State and its Principal Industrial Areas 21 - 0052, 1914-1947 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- The Effective Dates and Sanctions of the Taft-Hartley Act 21 - 0053, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Testimony of Charles A. Pearce, Direction, Division of Research and Statistics, New York State Department of Labor 21 - 0054, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Recent Studies of Living Costs in Large and Small Communities 21 - 0055, 1945-1947 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Applications for Restaurant Nightwork Permits 21 - 0056, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Division of Research and Statistics Reappraisal of the Migrant - Registration Law 21 - 0057, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Division of Research and Statistics Appraisal of the Migrant - Registration Law 21 - 0058, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- The Four-Industry Safety Survey 21 - 0059, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Physical Examinations in Industry (in reply to a request from Assemblyman Lawrence M. Rulison, Syracuse, N.Y.) 21 - 0060 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Deterrents to Hiring of Older Workers After Pension Plan is Created Also Memorandum 21 - 0061, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Industrial + Mercantile Establishments in the N.Y. City Metropolitan Area, 1951 21 - 0062, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Employee and Employer Organizations in Selected Industries Not Covered by the New York State Minimum Wage Orders 21 - 0063, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Sweatshops (?) and Industrial Homework in the Garment Industry 21 - 0064, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Classification of Injuries and Accidents, New York State Workmen's Compensation Board 21 - 0065 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- B.F: Right to Work 21 - 0066 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Wages of Women in New York State Factories 21 - 0067, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Recommendations on Minimum Wage Legislation 21 - 0068 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Summary of Major Provisions of Minimum Wage Orders Issued Under the New York State Minimum Wage Law 21 - 0069, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Summary of Major Provisions of Minimum Wage Laws and Orders Applicable to the Hotel Industry in the United States, Exclusive of New York State 21 - 0070, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Factors to be Considered in Connection with a Building Service Minimum Wage Board 21 - 0071, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Committee on Labor Law and Industrial Relations 21 - 0072, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Estimate of Minimum Wage Coverage in New York State as of February 1968 21 - 0073 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Farm Labor Operations Paid by the Piece 21 - 0074, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Proposed Project of Earnings of Piece Rate Workers on Farms, Summer 1971 21 - 0075, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Minutes of Meeting New York State Labor Department Research and Statistics Committee Albany October 20, 1970 21 - 0076 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- 21 - 0077 NY State Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics Special Minimum Rates for Youth, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Background Material Relating to the Employment of Youth in New York State 21 - 0078, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Cost of Wage Boards 21 - 0079, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 79)
- Industrial Conditions in New York State 21 - 0080, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Major Opinion Surveys Concerning the Taft-Hartley Law 21 - 0081, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Unemployment Insurance Benefits and Cost of Living 21 - 0082, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 82)
- U.S. Department of Commerce Bureau of the Census Washington, D.C. 20233 21 - 0083, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- Inter - Office Memorandum and Garment Industry Interview Form 21 - 0084, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- Development of the Minimum Wage in New York State 21 - 0085, 1944-1974 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- Inter-Office Memorandum Recommendations of Camp Board 21 - 0086, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Inter-Office Memorandum Current Status of Defense Program 21 - 0087 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Economic Research and Analysis 21 - 0089, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Workers Receiving Wages of 75 Cents or More Per Hour 21 - 0089, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- B.F: Vocational Rehabilitation International Business Machines Corporation 21 - 0090, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics Significant Events New York City May 1977 21 - 0091 (Box 11, Folder 91)
- Research and Statistics in Albany 21 - 0092, 1960-1976 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- Inter-Office Memorandum Preliminary Report on the "Job Service Campaign" 21 - 0093, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 93)
- Establishments Employing 500 or More Persons in New York City, By Industry (a) 21 - 0094, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- State of New York Department of Labor Survey of the Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board 25 - 0001, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Recommendations for Reorganization of Needle Trades Placement in New York City 25 - 0002, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Oral Argument of Counsel on the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law in the Supreme Court of the United States October Term 1936 25 - 0003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Report on Unemployment Insurance Problems 25 - 0004, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- State of New York, Department of Labor Analysis of Merit Rating Provisions in State Unemployment Compensation Laws January 15, 1937 25 - 0005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Wage Base Plan on Individual Employer Experience Rating 25 - 0006, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Employer Experience Rating Plan Proposed by the New York State Employers' Conference 25 - 0007, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Quality of Performance as Affected by Increased Staffing in Unemployment Insurance Offices 25 - 0008, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Guides to Interpretation and Procedure Relating to Eligibility for Benefits Part One: Typical Interpretations in Past Experience 25 - 0009, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Guides to Interpretation and Procedure Relating to Eligibility for Benefits Part One: Typical Interpretations in Past Experience 25 - 0010, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Guides to Interpretation and Procedure Relating to Eligibility for Benefit Part One: Typical Interpretations in Past Experience 25 - 0011, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Report of the Interstate Conference on Migrant and Multi-State Workers 25 - 0012, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- The New York State Unemployment Insurance Law as it Affects the Employee and the Employer 25 - 0013, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Unemployment Insurance Experience in New York State, 1938-1947 25 - 0014 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Implications of the Term "Suitable Employment" as Defined in 47 American Unemployment Compensation Acts 25 - 0015, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Report on Partial Unemployment 25-0016, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- The New York State Unemployment Insurance Tax Credit Plan 1947 25 - 0017 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- New York State Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0018 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  2 Booklets
- Material Used by the Ives Committee 25 - 0019, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Refusal of Employment and Referral to Employment Statements, Procedures and Decisions Issued By DPUI, USES, SSB, and UI Appeal Board Up to June 15, 1943 25 - 0020 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Basic Considerations Relating to the Benefit Structure Under the New York Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0021, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Effects of Various Benefit Formulae on Benefit Rate 25 - 0022, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Federal Reinsurance and Minimum Benefit Standards 25 - 0023, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Cases Involving Self Employment Derived from Sample Study of Local Office Cases During 1949-50 Benefit Year 25 - 0024, 1949- 1950 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Comments on the Federalization of Unemployment Insurance Pros and Cons 1941-1943 25 - 0025 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- State of New York Department of Labor Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance The Bigge Plan 25 - 0026, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Relations Between Federal Bill and State Law on Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0027 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Stamp Plans 25 - 0028, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Minutes of Meetings of District Superintendents and Headquarters Office Staff 25 - 0029, 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Maritime Labor Practices A Brief General Survey 25 - 0030, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Guides to Interpretation and Procedure Relating to Eligibility for Benefits Part One: Typical Interpretations in Past Experience 25 - 0031, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Seasonal Employment A Report on Section 508 of the Unemployment Insurance Law to the Industrial Commissioner of the State of New York 25 - 0032, 1940-1970 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Administrative Financing March 6, 1952 25 - 0033 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Reorganization of the Unemployment Insurance Procedure of New York State 25 - 0034 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Report to the Governor at the Close of the First Benefit Year of Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0035, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Budgetary Control of Fixed and Variable Expenses Under Varying Load Conditions in an Unemployment Compensation Agency 25 - 0036, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Training Material Brief History of the Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0037 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Official Interpretations of the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law 25 - 0038, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Analysis of Wage Base Plan of Individual Employer Experience Rating 25 - 0039, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Lines of Supervision in the Field 25 - 0040, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Supporting Statement Bill No. 4 - Resumption of Employment Service Functions 25 - 0041, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- The Employment Service and the Public Assistance Problem 25 - 0042, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Insured Employees, By Selected Industry January 1940 - June 1944 25 - 0043, 1940-1944 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Considerations Affecting Federalization of the Employment/Unemployment Security/Insurance Program 25 - 0044, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Unemployment Insurance in the Second Year of War Annual Report - 1943 25 - 0045 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Memorandum on State Plan for Unemployment Insurance for Maritime Workers History of Legislation 25 - 0046, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Re: Subscription to Interstate Great Lakes Reciprocal Arrangements 25 - 0047, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Benefit Experience in New York State, 1939-1940 25 - 0048 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- New York Water Transportation Employment Statistics Project Summary of Findings 25 - 0049, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  Top left of paper ripped off, but in folder.
- Methods of Estimating Cost to the New York Unemployment Insurance Fund of Certain Seasonal Industries 25 - 0050, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Seasonal Workers Appeal Board and Referee Rulings Reasons for Seasonal Provisions 25 - 0051, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance 25 - 0052, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Coverage of Domestic Employment, New York 25 - 0053, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Unemployment Insurance for Seamen (Officers and Members of Crews) 25 - 0054, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- The Beauty Service Industry, New York State, 1941 (Including Data with Respect to Tips) 25 - 0055 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- A Survey of Shoe Manufacturing in New York City 25 - 0056, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Public Health Insurance and Disability Benefit Plans in the United States, 1945 25 - 0057 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Employment and Claim Experience of Performers in Entertainment Industry 25 - 0058, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance Plans for Expanding the Employment Service 25 - 0059, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance Proposed Scheme for Expanding the Employment Service 25 - 0060, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- The Expansion and Development of the New York State Employment Service 25 - 0061, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Report of the Interstate Conference on Migrant and Multi-State Workers 25 - 0062, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Report to the Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council and Employment Service State Advisory Council 25 - 0063, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Report to the Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council and Employment Service State Advisory Council 25 - 0063 Pt. 2, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Bus and Airline Terminals. April 9, 1947 25 - 0064 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Bus and Airline Terminals 25 - 0065, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Check Rooms. April 10, 1947 25 - 0066 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Public Hearing on Tips in Check Rooms. April 18, 194725 - 0067 (Box 13, Folder 6)